现在让我们谈谈我们如何将内核实际应用于图像。
Let’s talk now about how we would actually apply the kernel to an image.
我们需要应用的算法是什么？
What is the algorithm that we would need to apply?
这就是它的样子;它是指定的输入窗口的总和
And this is what it looks like; it is a summation over the input window which is designated
通过符号W.在求和中，我们有输入图像I和内核K.
by the symbol W. And inside the summation we have the input image I and the kernel K.
指数I和J都在-H到+H的值范围内。我们在这里以数学方式写了什么
The indices I and J both range over values from -H to +H. What we have written here mathematically
是二维相关的定义。
is the definition of a two dimensional correlation.
存在称为卷积的相关操作，并且数学地表示2D卷积
There is a related operation called convolution, and 2D convolution is represented mathematically
这条路。
this way.
它与我们刚才看到的相关性非常相似;事实上，唯一的区别是
It is very similar to the correlation we just looked at; in fact, the only differences are
这些负面迹象在这里。
these negative signs here.
为了相关，他们是积极的迹象。
For correlation they were positive signs.
现在，如果内核是对称的，卷积与相关性相同。
Now convolution is the same as correlation if the kernel is symmetric.
例如，我们刚才看到的高斯核确实是对称的。
The Gaussian kernel we just looked at, for example, is indeed symmetric.
卷积的一个优点是它可以以运算符的形式编写。
An advantage of convolution is that it can be written in operator form.
所以这就是输出图像等于与输入图像卷积的内核
So what this says is the output image is equal to the kernel convolved with the input image
一世。
I.
因此，圆圈内的十字符号表示卷积的运算。
So the symbol of a cross inside a circle represents the operation of convolution.
卷积的一些属性是什么？
What are some of the properties of convolution?
好一开始它是可交换的，所以与B卷积的A与用A卷积的B相同。
Well for a start it is commutative, so A convolved with B is the same as B convolved with A.
它也是关联的，这是我们将在一些即将发布的幻灯片中使用的属性。
It is also associative and this is a property that we will use in some upcoming slides.
我们说它是分配的。
We say it is distributive.
它也是线性的。
And it is also linear.
所以这些是卷积的重要数学属性。
So these are important mathematical properties of convolution.
现在，关联性的优势是什么？
Now, what are the advantages of associativity?
好吧，考虑我用高斯卷积图像然后进行卷积的情况
Well consider the case where I convolve an image with a Gaussian and then I convolve
再次使用高斯。
with a Gaussian again.
所以，如果你愿意，我可以把它想象成添加一个图像，我通过应用高斯来平滑它
So if you like, I can think of this as adding an image, I smooth it by applying a Gaussian
它然后我再次平滑它。
to it and then I smooth it again.
这与使用高斯卷积的内核卷积图像相同
This is the same as convolving the image with a kernel which is the Gaussian convolved with
本身。
itself.
并且将高斯与另一高斯卷积在高斯中。
And convolving a Gaussian with another Gaussian results in a Gaussian.
并且结果高斯的标准偏差是标准偏差的函数
And the standard deviation of the result Gaussian is a function of a standard deviation of the
两个正在成倍增加的高斯，如左边所示。
two Gaussians that are multiplying, as shown over here on the left.
因此，为了用非常大的高斯卷积图像，这需要非常高
So in order to convolve an image with a very large Gaussian which would require a very
大内核，它实际上相当于用小高斯多次卷积图像
big kernel, it is actually equivalent to convolving the image with a small Gaussian multiple times
连续。
consecutively.
这样做可能有一些计算优势。
And there may be some computational advantages of doing that.